Age.
It’s more than just a number.
It’s a state of being.
It’s a mindset.
It’s part of your story.
But it’s not necessarily a
reflection of your health.
That’s why knowing your
Vitality AgeTM is so important.
Vitality Age is a simple
measure of your current health
based on your physical condition
and lifestyle choices like eating,
sleeping and being
active, to name a few.
Put it this way: when
you live a healthy life,
you may be younger than the number
of candles on your birthday cake.
But the reverse is also true,
depending on your overall health.
Knowing your Vitality Age is the best way
to find out how healthy you are right now,
and to help to set goals to further
improve your health, little by little.
And you don’t have to be a Manulife
Vitality member to learn yours.
Find out how healthy you are
today at Manulife.ca/Vitality